zibika.com 2016-05-26

# Privacy Policy - Zibika.com

**Zibika is fanatical about protecting your privacy!**  
  
Privacy: Freedom from unauthorized intrusion : state of being let alone and able to keep certain esp. Personal matters to oneself.   
  
Zibika respects and values the privacy of all our members. Please read our privacy statement carefully to understand the steps taken to ensure the security of all our users and members.   
**The 3 commandments of Zibika:**

1\. You shall always adhere to the code of conduct laid down.  
2\. You shall not, under any circumstances breach the security of its members.  
3\. You shall not disrupt the working of the website in any manner.   
  
**Information We Collect:**

Zibika collects personal information when you register as a member or otherwise voluntarily provide such information while using our products systems. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other services (own or third parties) to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.

Zibika uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services in order to improve their quality. Cookies contain bits of information that store your preferences on Zibika on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Although Zibika may assign a cookie to your browser, the cookie does not tell us who you are, who you are dating, what your net banking password is or what you are currently wearing. Only you can tell us that, the net banking bit, we urge you not to tell anyone from random online sources ever... Please.

Zibika's servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type, isp and language, and the date and time of your request.

The information we collect includes:

. Your name, email id, addresses, telephone numbers, birth date or any other personal information which will all be a part of your profiling system on Zibika  
. Information related to visits on particular sections or pages on the site.  
. Your searches, responses, queries, views, messages, blogs, comments, questions, answers and such content is recorded.  
. Any service you use from our site and how often you use them.  
. When you use the community and interact with different members and users.  
. Any customer related information that you provide to the site for example any feedback you have given or any claim you have made with our site.  
. Any transaction that you might conduct on site for online purchases of products when available using credit cards, net banking, etc.   
  
**Utilization of this Information:**

Zibika does not rent or sell personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies as databases for call centres to hound you! Of course, if you have requested for certain products or services using our online application systems, we would assume that we have your permission to let the respective service providers contact you.   
  
**Information we collect about you and from you can be utilized as follows:**

. To notify you of certain contests, awards, newsletters, etc., not that you have to act on it. If it sucks we urge you to let us know.. Please??  
. To help provide more customized services to you.  
. To personalize the content and advertisements provided to you.  
. The information we collect from blogs, communities etc may be published in various publications along with your screen name, only after seeking the required approval from you.  
. We might use non-personally identifiable aggregate information to improve the design, content, overall usability of our site and to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

If Zibika believes that the information that you share which your friends, relatives etc may pose as a serious threat to any person, organization or any such information which may be accessed, we might be compelled to disclose the same in response to a legal process or in any other circumstances in which Zibika believes it to be a crime. In the event of any ownership changes as a result of merger, acquisition or transfer to another company your information on this site will be transferred to the company/party henceforth managing the site. In such scenarios the website will give a prior notice to all its members. You will have a choice to decline the permit of any such transfer by deleting your account.   
  
**Personal Financial Information:**

Zibika under no circumstances will display you personal financial information regarding your portfolio manager, zbox etc to any affiliated third parties other than limited circumstances permitted by the law. Zibika also does share any information on stocks and funds in your portfolio with any affiliated service providers. If you wish to disclose any personal financial information with any individual, organization or third party, it is completely your choice. Zibika will not be held liable for any consequences arising out of such decisions. If you click through a banner advertisement on the portfolio and identify yourself to the advertiser, the advertiser may be able to tell that you use that feature. No portfolio is shared with anyone apart from those you have allowed access to in your portfolio advisors list.   
  
**Advertisements:**

The Ads that appear on Zibika are directly delivered from third party providers. When you click on any of these ads these third party advertisers may place cookies or use some other technologies to measure the effectiveness and impact of such ads. Zibika does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy statement.   
  
**Remarketing :**

Zibika Remarketing uses permanent cookies to enable basic web traffic analysis using Google Analytics (showing us which areas of the site are popular and those that are not often visited, this allows us to prioritise our enhancements to our website). We also use permanent cookies to 'remember you' when you return, but only if you have ticked the âRemember meâ facility on logging in.   
Zibika Remarketing do use some cookies from trusted 3rd party sources to enable us to provide you with certain features on our website & also show advertisements across internet using our advertisement channels.   
Removing some of our cookies may seriously disrupt use of the site.   
  
**Links:**

Zibika contains numerous links to other websites. Accessing these sites is at your own risk. Zibika will not be held liable for any breaches carried out by external linked sites. Please make sure to read the privacy statements of the relevant sites.   
  
**Importance of Security:**

Zibika has taken all measures and steps to prevent any misuse or unauthorized access to the site and its information. Zibika uses passwords to help verify your identity before granting access or using your profile information. Though we don't guarantee your security, you may post content on our site at your own risk.   
  
**Parental Guidance:**

The website is open only to individuals who are 13 years of age and above. Children below 13 years of age require parental guidance or supervision to enter or conduct any activities on our site. Zibika will not be held liable for any information posted by children below 13 years of age. If under any circumstances we learn that children below 13 years have collected or posted any information on our site without any parental consent, we will delete this information as quickly as possible and necessary action as deemed will be taken.   
  
**Changes:**

Zibika may change, revise or update its privacy policy from time to time. Please review the privacy statement periodically so that you are always aware and understand our privacy policy well.
